exactme.com 2012-12-04

# Privacy policy | EXACTME!

**Protect Your Privacy and Safety**

**Effective Date: _September 1, 2011_**

JoBooKIT Technologies LTD. ("JoBookIt", "We" or "Our") has drafted its Privacy Policy to ensure that you can use the "Exact Me!" Site on your own terms. JoBookIt continues to strive to provide the safest possible environment for you to search for and apply to jobs.

**JoBookIt Precautions**

**Overview**

We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of our collection, use and disclosure practices regarding personal information that we collect through "Exact Me!" website. This Privacy Policy applies only to data gathered on any web site under JoBookIt's control (collectively, the "Sites"), and does not apply to any other information or web site. This Privacy Policy incorporates by reference the Terms and Conditions for the Sites, which apply to this privacy policy.

Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. Each time you visit the Sites or provide us with information, you are, by doing so, accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time. If we materially change our practices with regard to personal information collected under a prior privacy policy, we will endeavor to notify you and give you the opportunity to opt out of changes with regard to that previously collected information. You agree that by using the Sites you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails, as described below. 

**Personal Information**

In order to operate the Sites in an efficient and effective manner and provide users with information on job postings and services that may be of interest to them, JoBookIt may collect personal information, including contact information (such as an email address) and other content posted by its users to the Site (e.g., resumes and profiles), from its users. In addition, this information allows us to provide users with private and secure areas to post, modify or delete their original content on our Sites (e.g., jobs, resumes and profiles) or to cancel their account. We also automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the Sites and use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve users in general. This information may include the URL that a user has just come from (whether this URL is on our Sites or not), the URL a user goes to next (whether this URL is on our Sites or not), a user's computer browser information, and their IP address. You agree that JoBookIt may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests (such as relevant job postings, services, educational or other career development opportunities), or provide administrative notices or communications applicable to your use of the Sites. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of any further receipt by following the opt out provisions provided in each such communication or by sending an e-mail to the address listed on the Site. JoBookIt may also aggregate certain non-personally identifiable information about its users (such as occupation, location, education and experience) and use such anonymous information to prepare reports that it provides to its users.

All users should be aware that when they choose to display or distribute personal information (such as their email address or resume) via the Sites or any other distribution method, that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which JoBookIt is not responsible. Also, you may have arrived at the Sites by following a link from a JoBookIt affiliate or other affiliate's web site. If so, please be aware that JoBookIt may share your information with that affiliate and the affiliate may use the information consistent with its privacy policy instead of this one.

JoBookIt may also disclose specific user information when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, to cooperate with or seek assistance from law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of JoBookIt or other users of the Sites. In addition, personal information we have collected may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets or a bankruptcy of JoBookIt. Such disclosures may be made with or without your consent, and with or without notice.

**Credit Card Security**

JoBookIt employs encryption for secure credit card transactions.

**About Cookies and Third Party Advertisers**

JoBookIt uses cookie for the protection and convenience of our users. Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. If a user's system is idle for more than an hour, however, the cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorized access to the user's information while they are away from their computer. JoBookIt may store non-personally identifying information about you such as past jobs viewed and job searches conducted by your computer in a cookie that it places on your computer. We do this in order to present you with job recommendations based on your interests as expressed previously through your searches. Most Internet browsers enable you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please be aware; however, that some "Exact Me!" features or services may not function properly without cookies.

Third-Party Advertisers: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Sites. These companies may use information about your visits to these and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We also may give third party advertisers the ability to tailor their advertisements on our Sites using demographic and preference information we provide to them in aggregate form. This information does not identify you individually.

These third party advertising companies may use this information to provide you with advertising on our Sites, other websites, or other service platforms or devices tailored to the interests indicated by your browsing our of Sites and/or your interaction with other web sites where these ad servers or networks are also present. 

The third party advertising companies who deliver ads for JoBookIt on the Sites may place or access cookies on your computer hard drive to distinguish your web browser uniquely and to keep track of information relating to serving ads on your web browser, such as the type of ads shown and the webs pages on which the ads appeared. The third party advertising companies may use cookies to keep track of the web sites that your web browser visits across the advertising provider's network of web sites with whom it works. These companies may combine this information with other information they have collected relating to your web browser's activities across their network of web sites. 

These companies operate under their own privacy policies and JoBookIt encourages you to be aware of the privacy policies of such companies before you choose to allow them to place a cookie on your web browser. JoBookIt does not have control over or access to any information contained in the cookies that are set on your computer by third party advertisers.

In addition, some of the employers that use our Sites may place cookies on your computer through their job postings and may use such cookies to distinguish your web browser uniquely. Often, employers use such information to track the effectiveness of their job postings by measuring how many users who view their postings later became job applicants.

**What You Should Know**

JoBookIt cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. As a user of the Sites, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Sites, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Sites.
